Jerome Kern Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Show Music (Box 1-95, Box 103-116)
  - Manuscripts (Box 1-94, Box 103-116)
    - Sweet Adeline (1929) lyrics by Oscar Hammerstein II
      - I wish I knew: #8, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink, lyric in Kern's hand in pencil; 6 p.; Uniform title: Why was I born? (Box-folder 75/16)
      - Why was I born?, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in pencil, for publication; 4 p. (Box-folder 75/16)
      - Yacht scene; [Don't ever leave me], Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; [15] p.; On back: ms. lead sheet/sketch in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 75/17)
      - Yacht scene; Don't ever leave me, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink, lyric in pencil and ink, some by Kern; 17 p.; Note: listed in the program as "The harbor scene" (Box-folder 75/17)
      - Yes, m'am: Elly and boys See also: "Poor wet fish", Ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) piano-vocal score in ink, lyric in pencil, mostly in Hammerstein's hand, partially in Kern's hand, + holograph insert in pencil; 10 p. + [1] p.; Note: originally intended for Show Boat, became "First Mate Martin" in Sweet Adeline (Box-folder 75/18)
      - [Unidentified/miscellaneous holographs], Holograph sketches in pencil; [1] p.; Note: includes fragments of "Why was I born?," "Here am I" and "Jenny Lee"; On back: part for "My gal is a high born lady" from Show Boat (Box-folder 75/19)
      - [Unidentified/miscellaneous holographs], Holograph (mostly) sketches in ink and pencil; [4] p. (Box-folder 75/19)
      - [Unidentified/miscellaneous holographs], Holograph sketches in pencil; [1] p.; Note: includes release to "Here am I" and end of "Don't ever leave me" (Box-folder 75/19)
      - [Unidentified/miscellaneous holographs], Holograph sketches in pencil; [1] p.; Note: includes "Don't ever leave me" (Box-folder 75/19)
      - [Unidentified/miscellaneous manuscripts]: Act I opening scene 3, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink, annotations in pencil, partial lyric; 8 p. (Box-folder 75/20)
      - [Unidentified/miscellaneous holographs]: [Act I opening scene 3]: Chorus parts insert see page 2, Copyist's ms. choral arrangement in pencil; 3 p.; Note: the two items above go together, representing an unknown song which might be "We're glad we're here" (Box-folder 75/20)
      - [Unidentified], Ms. sketches in pencil; [2] p. (Box-folder 75/20)
      - Sweet Adeline Selection, Ms. (Albert Sirmay) piano score in pencil with paste-ins from printed score; 19 p.; Includes: "Here am I" "Why was I born" "A girl is on your mind" "Don't ever leave me" "'Twas not so long ago" (Box-folder 75/21)
      - [Lyric sheets], Typed lyric sheets; [13] p.; Includes: "Here am I" "Molly O'Donohue" "Out of the blue" (2 sets) "[Some girl is on your mind]: Hoffman house scene" "The sun about to rise" "'Twas not so long ago (from the German)" (Box-folder 75/22)
    - Three Sisters (1934) lyrics by Oscar Hammerstein II
      - Dorrie barges see: I won't dance from Roberta
      - Opening act II see: Series II -- Miscellaneous Music
    - Toot-Toot! (1918) lyrics by Berton Braley
      - Every young girl in America, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; 4 p. (p. 4 crossed out); Note: a.k.a. "Every girl in all America" (Box-folder 76/1)
      - Finale act II: Opening chor act II, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; 9 p. (Box-folder 76/2)
      - Girlie: no. 13, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; 2 p. (Box-folder 76/3)
      - Girlie, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink; 4 p. (Box-folder 76/3)
      - Girlie, Printed piano-vocal score, annotations in pencil, some in Bennett's hand; 5 p. (Box-folder 76/3)
      - Honeymoon land: #7 See also: "Omaha", Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink; [4] p. (Box-folder 76/4)
      - If, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; 2 p.; Note: a.k.a. "If you only cared enough" and "If (there's anything you want)" (Box-folder 76/5)
      - Porter's song, Holograph and ms. (Frank Saddler) sketch in pencil; [3] p. + intro in Kern's hand on scrap of paper; Uniform title: It's immaterial to me (Box-folder 76/6)
      - *The last long mile, Printed piano-vocal score; 5 p.; Music and lyric by Emil Breitenfeld (Box-folder 76/7)
      - Omaha, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 9 p. (Box-folder 76/8)
      - Omaha; New burthen for "Honeymoon land", Holograph piano sketch in pencil; 3 p. (Box-folder 76/9)
      - Omaha: #13a, Parts (Box-folder 76/10)
      - Opening act II, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink, no lyric; [4] p.; Note: this may not be from Toot-Toot! (Box-folder 76/11)
      - Op chos act I: #1, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; 5 p. + [1] p. insert; Uniform title: Opening chorus act 1 (Box-folder 76/12)
      - Runaway colts, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; 2 p. (Box-folder 76/13)
      - Smoke, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; 6 p. (Box-folder 76/14)
      - Teepee, Parts (orchestration by Charles Miller); Note: a.k.a. "I will knit a suit of dreams" (Box-folder 76/15)
      - [Toot-Toot!]: No. 11⁄2, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano-vocal score in pencil; 7 p. (Box-folder 76/16)
      - [When you] wake up dancing, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; 2 p.; Note: musical routine on back of p. 2 (Box-folder 76/17)
      - [When you] wake up dancing, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink; [4] p. (Box-folder 76/17)
      - Yankee doodle on the line, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano score in pencil; 2 p. (Box-folder 76/18)
      - [Lyric sheets], Typed lyric sheets; [3] p.; Includes: "Immaterial to me" "Nellie from Omaha" (Box-folder 76/19)
    - Vanity Fair
      - [Various titles] see: Dear Sir
    - Very Good Eddie (1915) lyrics mostly by Schuyler Greene & Herbert Reynolds [M.E. Rourke]
      - Babes in the woods: duettino, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink and pencil; 10 p.; Note on cover: "Copyist Extract only ink notes pay no attention to pencil marks. J. Kern Feb 20th/1917" (Box-folder 77/1)
      - Babes in the wood and change of scene: no. 10, Arranger's holograph (C.M. Selling) full score in ink and pencil; 20 p. (Box-folder 77/2)
      - Buffo dance: no. 91⁄2 See also: "Buffo dance" from Nobody Home, Arranger's holograph (C.M. Selling) full score in ink; 5 p. (Box-folder 77/3)
      - The fashion show, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 16 p. (Box-folder 77/4)
      - The fashion show: no. 11, Arranger's holograph (C.M. Selling) full score in ink; 18 p. (Box-folder 77/4)
      - Finale act II, Arranger's holograph (C.M. Selling) full score in ink; 12 p.; Note: original orchestration, includes "Babes in the wood," "If I find the girl," "I've got to dance" and "Nodding roses" (Box-folder 77/5)
      - Finale act II: no. 14, Arranger's holograph (C.M. Selling) full score in ink; 4 p.; Note: Casino version, includes "Babes in the wood" and "If I find the girl" (Box-folder 77/5)
      - Finaletto act I See also: Miscellaneous/Unidentified Show Music, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 28 p.; Note: p. 22-28 crossed out with note in Kern's hand "copy in Here p+f Refrain 'Grand and Glorious Feeling' in D" (Box-folder 77/6)
      - I'd like to have a million: no. 12, Arranger's holograph (C.M. Selling) full score in ink; 14 p. (Box-folder 77/7)
      - I would like to have a million, Arranger's holograph (Charles Miller) full score in ink; 15 p.; Note: a.k.a. "I wish I had a million" and "I'd like to have a million in the bank" (Box-folder 77/7)
      - If I find the girl: no. 7, Arranger's holograph (C.M. Selling) full score in ink; 15 p. (Box-folder 77/8)
      - If I find the girl, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 12 p. (Box-folder 77/8)
      - Isn't it great to be married: quartette: no. 4, Arranger's holograph (C.M. Selling) full score in ink; 9 p. (Box-folder 77/9)
      - Quartette, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 11 p. (Box-folder 77/9)
      - I've just been waiting for you see: I've just been waiting for you from A Modern Eve
      - Nodding roses: no. 13, Arranger's holograph (C.M. Selling) full score in ink; 8 p. (Box-folder 77/10)
      - Nodding roses, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; p. a-b, 1-8 (Box-folder 77/10)
      - Old Bill Baker, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano-vocal score in ink; [4] p.; Lyric by Ring Lardner; Note: song added to show after opening; Note on p. [4] from Frank Saddler: "Jerry: In case of death by bed-bug poisoning use these two bars? -- $." (Box-folder 77/11)
      - Old boy neutral: no. 9, Arranger's holograph (C.M. Selling) full score in ink; 13 p. (Box-folder 77/12)
      - Old boy neutral, Arranger's holograph (Charles Miller) full score in ink; 12 p. (Box-folder 77/12)
      - On the shore of Le Lei Wi: act II opening number: no. 6, Arranger's holograph (C.M. Selling) full score in ink; 15 p. (Box-folder 77/13)
      - On the shore at Le Lei Wi: New number, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 12 p. (Box-folder 77/14)
      - Opening act II: The little review, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 34 p. (Box-folder 77/15)
      - Opening ensemble: act I, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 28 p. (Box-folder 77/16)
      - The same old game: no. 2, Arranger's holograph (C.M. Selling) full score in ink; 18 p. (Box-folder 77/17)
      - The same old game, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 16 p. (Box-folder 77/17)
      - Some sort of somebody: no. 3, Arranger's holograph (C.M. Selling) full score in ink; 10 p. (Box-folder 77/18)
      - Wedding bells [are calling me]: finale act I: no. 5, Arranger's holograph (C.M. Selling) full score in ink; 21 p. (Box-folder 77/19)
      - Wedding bells are calling [me]: 1st act finale, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 14 p. (Box-folder 77/19)
      - We're on our way: opening number act I: no. 1, Arranger's holograph (C.M. Selling) full score in ink; 30 p. (Box-folder 77/20)
      - West Point dance, Arranger's holograph (C.M. Selling) full score in ink; 10 p. (Box-folder 77/21)
      - West Point dance, Arranger's holograph (Charles Miller) full score in ink; 11 p. (Box-folder 77/21)
      - [When you wear] a 13 collar: no. 8, Arranger's holograph (C.M. Selling) full score in ink; 10 p. (Box-folder 77/22)
      - [When you wear] a "13" collar, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 9 p. (Box-folder 77/22)
    - Very Warm for May (1939) lyrics by Oscar Hammerstein II
      - Act II: #6, Ozalids (2) of ms. piano score; 5 p. (Box-folder 78/1)
      - All in fun, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink and pencil; p. 1-26, 22-30 (Box-folder 110/1)
      - All in fun, Ms. (Albert Sirmay) piano-vocal score in pencil; 7 p.; Ozalids (3) of ms. piano-vocal score; 5 p. (Box-folder 78/2)
      - All in fun: #28, Parts (Box-folder 80/1)
      - All in fun: new #24, Parts (Box-folder 80/2)
      - All in fun: #24, Parts (Box-folder 80/3)
      - All the things you are, Arranger's holograph (Gus Levene) full score in ink; 10 p. (Box-folder 110/2)
      - All the things you are, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 12 p. (incomplete?) (Box-folder 110/2)
      - All the things you are, Ms. (Albert Sirmay) piano-vocal score in pencil, for publication; 8 p. (Box-folder 78/3)
      - All the things you are, are mine: duet, Ms. (Albert Sirmay) piano-vocal score in pencil; 9 p.; Ozalids (2) of ms. piano-vocal score; 7 p. (Box-folder 78/3)
      - All the things you are, are mine, Ozalid of ms. piano-vocal score, no lyric; 5 p. (Box-folder 78/3)
      - All the things you are, are mine, Ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) choral arrangement in ink; 4 p. (Box-folder 113/8)
      - All the things you are, are mine, Copyist's ms. choral parts in ink (Box-folder 113/8)
      - All the things you are: #9, Parts (Box-folder 80/4)
      - All the things you are, Printed parts (arrangement by Jack Mason) (Box-folder 80/5)
      - All the things you are, are mine: ballet: finale act I, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink, no lyric; 3 p. (Box-folder 78/4)
      - Ballet: #11, Ozalid of ms. piano-vocal score, annotations in pencil, no lyric; 5 p. (Box-folder 78/4)
      - The arm of the law: The dance must go on See also: "Pizzicato" in Series II -- Miscellaneous Music, Ozalid of ms. piano-vocal score, lyric in pencil; 5 p. (3 of p. 5) (Box-folder 78/5)
      - Babbling brook dance, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 9 p. (Box-folder 110/3)
      - Babbling brook dance: #7a, Parts (Box-folder 80/6)
      - Boogiewoogie dance, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 37 p. (Box-folder 110/4)
      - New bars boogie, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; p. a-b, x (Box-folder 110/4)
      - Boogie woogie: #10b, Ms. sketch in pencil; 5 p. + [1] p. (Box-folder 78/6)
      - [Boogie woogie]: #10b: section 3, Ms. (Bobby Dolan?) short score insert in ink and pencil; [1] p.; Note: "This in place of piano break in Boogie Woogie if desired" (Box-folder 78/6)
      - Boogiewoogie dance: #10b, Parts (Box-folder 80/7)
      - Brain ballet: #21; New end brain ballet, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; p. 1-67, 1-5, 68-77, 68-71; Note: this is the same music as "In the heart of the dark" (Box-folder 110/5)
      - Brain ballet: #21, Parts (Box-folder 81/1)
      - Change music: #21a, Parts (Box-folder 81/2)
      - Curtain rises act one, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 38 p. (Box-folder 110/6)
      - Curtain rises act one: #1, Parts (Box-folder 81/3)
      - Dance Dada sequence see: Dress rehearsal opening see: Finale ultimo a
      - Dress rehearsal opening: new 22 change See also: "Finale ultimo a", Parts; Note: Dance Dada sequence was made up of Dress rehearsal opening and Finale ultimo a-h (Box-folder 81/4)
      - Encore no. 6, Ozalids (2) of ms. piano score; 4 p. (Box-folder 78/7)
      - End of Matty, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 1 p. (Box-folder 110/7)
      - End of Matty: #21b, Parts (Box-folder 81/5)
      - Entr'acte, Parts (Box-folder 81/6)
      - Essence seventeen: #25 See also: "In other words, seventeen", Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 7 p. (Box-folder 110/8)
      - Essence seventeen: #25, Parts (Box-folder 81/7)
      - Finale act I, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 14 p. (Box-folder 110/9)
      - Finale act I: seventeen -- Winnie's reprise, Photocopy of arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score; p. 2-13, 13a (Box-folder 110/9)
      - Finale act I: #16a, Parts (Box-folder 81/8)
      - Finale night club (15th bar on), Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; p. a-g (Box-folder 110/10)
      - Dress rehearsal opening; Finale ultimo a, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; p. 1-4, 1-2; Note: a.k.a. "All the things you are: underscoring"; Note: Dance Dada sequence was made up of Dress rehearsal opening and Finale ultimo a-h; Uniform title: Finale ultimo a (Box-folder 111/1)
      - Finale ultimo a: #23a, Parts (Box-folder 82/1)
      - Finale ultimo b, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 5 p.; Note: a.k.a. "Pale moon beams" (Box-folder 111/2)
      - Finale ultimo b, Parts (Box-folder 82/2)
      - Finale ultimo c, Arranger's holograph (Gus Levene) full score in pencil; 10 p.; Note: title "There's something about a musket" erased; Note: a.k.a. the dance "The brook and the lady in violet"; it used the theme from "Musket" or "Cricket tune" (Box-folder 111/3)
      - Finale ultimo c, Parts (Box-folder 82/3)
      - Finale ultimo d-e, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 7 p.; Note: out-of-town this number was known as "The tree and the lady in orchid"; on Broadway it became "The lady in red (toe dance for Kate Friedlich)" (Box-folder 111/4)
      - Finale ultimo d-e: #23b, Parts (Box-folder 82/4)
      - Finale ultimo f: that lucky fellow, Arranger's holograph (Gus Levene) full score in ink; 17 p.; Note: a.k.a "The blackbird and the lady in white" or "That lucky fellow" (Box-folder 111/5)
      - Finale ultimo f: that lucky fellow: new #27a, Parts (Box-folder 82/5)
      - Finale ultimo g, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 14 p.; Note: a.k.a. "The deer and the Park Avenue lady"; also uses the same melody as "Pale moon beams" (Box-folder 111/6)
      - Finale ultimo g: #23c, Parts (Box-folder 82/6)
      - Finale ultimo h, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 14 p.; Note: a.k.a. "The wind and the lady in motley" (Box-folder 111/7)
      - Finale ultimo h, Parts (Box-folder 82/7)
      - Finale ultimo i, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 14 p.; Note: "Finale ultimo i-n" were the real "Finale ultimo" of the out-of-town show, but were not used on Broadway (Box-folder 111/8)
      - Finale ultimo i, Parts (Box-folder 82/8)
      - Finale ultimo jk + lmn, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; p. 1, 13-33 (Box-folder 111/9)
      - Finaletto scene I, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 18 p. (Box-folder 111/10)
      - Finaletto: scene I, Ozalids (3) of ms. piano-score; 4 p. (Box-folder 78/8)
      - Finaletto scene I: #3, Parts (Box-folder 82/9)
      - *The flight of the bumble-bee, Printed piano arrangement by Paolo Gallico, annotations in pencil; 7 p.; Music by Rimsky-Korsakov (Box-folder 111/11)
      - *The flight of the bumble-bee, Ms. full score in ink and red pencil; 18 p.; Music by Rimsky-Korsakov (Box-folder 111/11)
      - The flight of the bumble-bee: #10a, Parts; Music by Rimsky-Korsakov (Box-folder 83/1)
      - Heaven in my arms: no. 15; Loper Barrot: #15a; Serpentine: #15b See also: "Music in my heart", Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 54 p. (Box-folder 111/12)
      - Heaven in my arms (Music in my heart), Printed piano-vocal scores (3), variant annotations; 5 p. (Box-folder 78/9)
      - [Heaven in my arms]: Night club, Ms. (mostly Robert Russell Bennett) piano score in ink; 11 p.; Ms. insert "after 6" short score/full score sketch in pencil laid in; [1] p.; Note: according to John McGlinn this was an old version of "Heaven in my arms" that was cut out of town (Box-folder 78/9)
      - Heaven in my arms: #15c, Parts (Box-folder 83/2)
      - Heaven in my heart: correction for last two lines of p. 5, Ms. (Albert Sirmay) piano-vocal score in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 78/10)
      - Introduction to 27, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 2 p.; Uniform title: High up in Harlem (Box-folder 111/13)
      - High up in Harlem: #27, Arranger's holograph (Nathan Lang Van Cleve) full score in ink; 26 p.; Uniform title: High up in Harlem (Box-folder 111/13)
      - High up in harlem, Ms. (Albert Sirmay) piano-vocal score in pencil, for publication; 5 p.; Typed lyric sheet laid in; [1] p. (Box-folder 78/11)
      - High up in harlem, Ms. (Hugh Martin) piano-vocal score in ink and pencil; [16] p.; Ozalids (2) of ms. piano-vocal score, no lyric; 4 p.; Typed lyric sheets (2) and note laid in 1 copy (Box-folder 78/11)
      - High-up-in Harlem: #27, Parts (Box-folder 83/3)
      - High up in Harlem: #28, Parts (Box-folder 83/4)
      - Hightower & Craven: #15d, Parts (Box-folder 83/5)
      - L'histoire de Madame de la Tour, Ozalid of ms. piano-vocal score; 7 p. (Box-folder 78/12)
      - Introduction to L'histoire de Madame de la Tour, Ms. piano score in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 78/12)
      - [L'histoire de Madame de la Tour dance]: Tempo di gavotte, Ms. piano sketch in pencil; p. 1-2, 7 (Box-folder 78/12)
      - [In other words,] seventeen, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink and pencil; p. 1-13, 13a, 14-40, 36 (Box-folder 111/14)
      - In other words, seventeen, Ms. (Albert Sirmay) piano-vocal score in pencil, for publication; 7 p. (Box-folder 78/13)
      - In other words, seventeen, Printed piano-vocal scores (2); 5 p. (Box-folder 78/13)
      - In other words, seventeen, Ozalid of ms. piano-vocal score; 10 p. (Box-folder 78/13)
      - In other words, seventeen: revised, Ozalids (3) of ms. piano-vocal score, variant annotations in pencil; 12 p. (Box-folder 78/13)
      - [In other words,] seventeen: #2, Parts (Box-folder 83/6)
      - In the heart of the dark See also: Brain ballet, Ms. (Albert Sirmay) piano-vocal score in pencil, for publication; 6 p. (Box-folder 78/14)
      - In the heart of the dark See also: Brain ballet, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink; [4] p.; Typed lyric sheet laid in; [1] p.; Ozalid of ms. piano-vocal score with marimba, lyric in pencil; 5 p. (Box-folder 78/14)
      - In the heart of the dark See also: Brain ballet, 1st proof for printed piano-vocal score with annotations in pencil; p. 2-4 (Box-folder 78/14)
      - In the heart of the dark See also: Brain ballet, Printed piano-vocal scores (2); 5 p. (Box-folder 78/14)
      - [In the] heart of the dark -- brown See also: Brain ballet, Ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) piano-vocal score in ink; 2 p. (Box-folder 78/14)
      - Johnny Graham's Wutsie, Ms. (partly Robert Russell Bennett) condensed score in pencil, annotations in ink; 8 p. (Box-folder 113/9)
      - Loper & Barrat: #15e See also: "Heaven in my arms" (full score), Parts (Box-folder 83/7)
      - May escapes, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 18 p. (Box-folder 112/1)
      - May escapes: #4, Parts (Box-folder 84/1)
      - May tells all, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 14 p. (Box-folder 112/2)
      - Patsy tells all, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink; 7 p.; Ozalid of ms. piano-vocal score; 7 p.; Uniform title: May tells all (Box-folder 78/15)
      - May Patsy tells all, Ozalid of ms. piano-vocal score, annotations in pencil; 7 p. (Box-folder 78/15)
      - May tells all: #12, Parts (Box-folder 84/2)
      - May's dance: #1a, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink and pencil; 18 p. (Box-folder 112/3)
      - May's dance: #1a, Parts (Box-folder 84/3)
      - Me and the roll and you, Ozalids (2) of ms. piano-vocal score, variant annotations in pencil; 4 p. (Box-folder 78/16)
      - Music in my heart See also: "Heaven in my arms", Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink and pencil; 28 p. (Box-folder 112/4)
      - Dance "Music in my heart" "Night club", Arranger's holograph (Nathan Lang Van Cleve) full score in ink; 63 p.; Uniform title: Music in my heart (Box-folder 112/5)
      - Music in my heart, Ms. (Albert Sirmay) piano-vocal score in pencil, for publication; 5 p.; Ozalids (3) of ms. piano-vocal scores, variant annotations in pencil; 4 p.; Note: 1 ozalid includes "Encore," another has no lyric (Box-folder 78/17)
      - Music in my heart: #14, Parts (Box-folder 84/4)
      - Music in my heart: new #14, Parts (Box-folder 84/5)
      - Dance "Music in my heart": #14a & #15g, Parts; Uniform title: Music in my heart (Box-folder 84/6)
      - Musket: opening act II -- part II, Ms. full score in ink; 38 p. (Box-folder 112/6)
      - New York: #27b, Parts (Box-folder 85/1)
      - New York finaletto, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 5 p. (Box-folder 112/7)
      - New York finaletto: #4 and #5 (new), Parts (Box-folder 85/2)
      - Intro to night club finale, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 1 p.; Uniform title: Night club finale (Box-folder 112/8)